
  <rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
      <title>SoftexForge | Software Solution | Innovation in System &amp; Application Software</title>
      <link>https://softexforge.com//blog</link>
      <description>We bring your ideas to life with tailored software solutions. Whether it&amp;apos;s system software, from kernel modifications to driver development, or application software for mobile, desktop, web, or standalone platforms, we&amp;apos;ve got you covered. From concept to production, we handle every step of the process to deliver high-quality, custom-built software.</description>
      <language>en-us</language>
      <managingEditor>nasim.stg@gmail.com (nasimstg)</managingEditor>
      <webMaster>nasim.stg@gmail.com (nasimstg)</webMaster>
      <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
      <atom:link href="https://softexforge.com//tech/guide/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
      
  <item>
    <guid>https://softexforge.com//blog/best-effective-way-learn-anything-quickly-easily</guid>
    <title>The Secret to Quick Learning: Most Effective Ways to Learn Anything Quickly and Efficiently</title>
    <link>https://softexforge.com//blog/best-effective-way-learn-anything-quickly-easily</link>
    <description>Discover the best and easiest way to learn anything quickly with our comprehensive guide. Learn about effective learning strategies, how to set clear goals, create a favorable learning environment, and more. Start optimizing your learning process today.</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <author>nasim.stg@gmail.com (nasimstg)</author>
    <category>how-to</category><category>guide</category><category>be-smart</category>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>https://softexforge.com//blog/creating-a-website-with-html-and-css</guid>
    <title>Creating a Website with HTML and CSS: Examples and Best Practices (Part 06)</title>
    <link>https://softexforge.com//blog/creating-a-website-with-html-and-css</link>
    <description> In this comprehensive guide, we cover the basics of creating a website using HTML and CSS. From the structure of an HTML document to the styling of elements with CSS, this blog post covers all the essential information you need to get started. The post includes code examples of websites created using HTML and CSS, along with best practices and tips for making your website both visually appealing and user-friendly. Whether you&#39;re a beginner looking to build your first website or a seasoned developer looking to expand your knowledge, this blog post provides valuable insights and resources. </description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <author>nasim.stg@gmail.com (nasimstg)</author>
    <category>html-css-js</category><category>guide</category><category>web-development</category>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>https://softexforge.com//blog/css-essentials-a-comprehensive-guide-to-web-design-and-development</guid>
    <title>CSS Fundamentals: A Guide for Web Development (part_04)</title>
    <link>https://softexforge.com//blog/css-essentials-a-comprehensive-guide-to-web-design-and-development</link>
    <description>Learn the essentials of CSS, including selectors, properties, box model, typography, responsive design, and more. Boost your web design skills with this comprehensive guide.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <author>nasim.stg@gmail.com (nasimstg)</author>
    <category>html-css-js</category><category>guide</category><category>web-development</category>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>https://softexforge.com//blog/self-reliance/5-best-methods-to-earn-money-online-in-bangla</guid>
    <title>Start Making Money Online Today: A Guide to the Most Effective Online Money Making Methods for Beginners</title>
    <link>https://softexforge.com//blog/self-reliance/5-best-methods-to-earn-money-online-in-bangla</link>
    <description>Today we have discussed five of the best and easiest ways to make money online including: affiliate marketing, selling products online, online surveys and market research, online tutoring or teaching, and online content creation. Each of these methods is explained in detail with examples and resources to help readers understand and apply them. The article also highlights the importance of patience, consistency and research to succeed in making money online. It serves as a comprehensive guide for those looking for ways to earn from home.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <author>nasim.stg@gmail.com (nasimstg)</author>
    <category>online-money-making</category><category>guide</category><category>atmanirbhar</category>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>https://softexforge.com//blog/excessive-list-of-html-tags</guid>
    <title>Excessive list of HTML Tags</title>
    <link>https://softexforge.com//blog/excessive-list-of-html-tags</link>
    <description>In the last episode (Episode 02) we have seen many tags of HTML and today we are going to see some, Today we will learn more about HTML tags. We will also see some examples. Series: How to learn web design and development complete course in Bengali?</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <author>nasim.stg@gmail.com (nasimstg)</author>
    <category>html-css-js</category><category>guide</category><category>web-development</category>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>https://softexforge.com//blog/all-about-html-tags</guid>
    <title>HTML Tags for Web Design and Development </title>
    <link>https://softexforge.com//blog/all-about-html-tags</link>
    <description>Today we will learn about HTML document (html document), HTML tag (html tag), types of HTML tags. Also we will see some examples (html example). How to learn series web design and development complete course? Learn Web Design and Development with nasimStg(wooeneStudio) HTML CSS JS </description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <author>nasim.stg@gmail.com (nasimstg)</author>
    <category>html-css-js</category><category>guide</category><category>web-development</category>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>https://softexforge.com//blog/basics-of-web-design-and-development</guid>
    <title>The Basics of Web Design and Development</title>
    <link>https://softexforge.com//blog/basics-of-web-design-and-development</link>
    <description>Today we will start learning web design and development in Bangla (learn website design and development in Bangla). We are going to start with the basics or fundamentals of web design and development for beginners. We will use html to create a website skeleton for our website. Next day we will start with website style. Let&#39;s start!</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <author>nasim.stg@gmail.com (nasimstg)</author>
    <category>html-css-js</category><category>guide</category><category>web-development</category>
  </item>

    </channel>
  </rss>
